stopforumspam.com 2019-03-21

# Stop Forum Spam

We have been informed, that we should publish a privacy policy, in order to keep some Big Brother governments happy, so here goes.

Your privacy is important to us. We have a few fundamental principles:

  * We don't ask you for personal information unless we truly need it.
  * We don't share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don't store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.
  * We aim to make it as simple as possible for you to control what is visible to the public, seen by search engines, kept private, and permanently deleted.

Below is our privacy policy which incorporates the goals of Creative Commons License

If you have questions about accessing or correcting your personal data please contact us. Below is our privacy policy which incorporates the goals of Creative Commons License:

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, we collect non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. The purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how our visitors use its website. From time to time, we may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website. This data is also used to identify any abuse of our server and services

We also collect potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on our forum, browsing our site and using our API. We only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that forum poster IP addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of our forum.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to our website choose to interact in ways that require us to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that we gather depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for a forum or API account, to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with us - by donating, for example, are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, we may collect such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with us. Most of this is via PayPal, were we have very limited access to any information. We do not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Aggregated Statistics

We may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, we may monitor the most accessed pages, most regular visitors and use these details to report on regular, high and abnormal web server behavior. We may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, we do not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

We may disclose potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those administrators whom have access to details provided when accessing our website, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on our behalf or to provide services available at website, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those administrators, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using our website, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. We will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its administrators, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, we disclose potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when we believe in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of stopforumspam, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of our website and have supplied your email address, we may occasionally (about once in a blue moon) send you an email to inform you if any changes to our service will severely impact your access to our site. We take all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorised access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. We use cookies to keep you logged into the forum, to tell if you're not logged into the forum in order to present paid advertising and to ensure that only you have access to your submission keys, statistics in information. Visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using our website, with the drawback that certain features of our website may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

 **Note Recent EU directives** \- we dont track cookies, their content is never logged

### Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognise your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by stopforumspam and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### API Query data

All data queried via the API is recorded in the way of web server logs. These logs are kept for a period of seven days and are used for abuse and intrusion monitoring. After seven days, they are removed from the server. Some off site backups may contain partial log data. Off site backups are encrypted. No log data has been disclosed to anyone (and never will be)

### Comments

Comments and other content submitted to our service are not saved on our servers unless they were marked as false positives, in which case we store them long enough to use them to improve the service to avoid future false positives.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, we may change this Privacy Policy from time to time at our sole discretion. We encourage visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
